# ABDELHAFID NEJJARI

# **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

mr.nejjari.abdelhafid@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn | Twitter | Portfolio

#### **SUMMARY**

Full-stack web developer and React enthusiast passionate about clean and easy-to-follow code, with experience in pair programming and remote work. Fluent in several languages, frameworks, and technologies, and a team player with an optimistic personality that can boost the morale of any team.

## **SKILLS**

Front-End: JavaScript, React, Redux, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3

Back-End: Ruby, Rails, PostgreSQL

Tools & Methods: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Mobile/Responsive Development, RSpec, TDD, Chrome Dev Tools

Professional: Remote Pair-Programming, Teamwork, Mentoring

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### HIGHLIGHTED PERSONAL PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer

Remote

November, 2022 - Present

<u>Awesome-books-V2</u> — Awesome books-V2 is a project That contains a single-page web application that keeps track of books.

Built with: (HTML5, CSS, JavaScript.)

math-magicians—A calculator application built implementing the React framework with SPA dynamics..

Built with: (JavaScript, React )

<u>To-Do-List-List-structure</u> —"To-do list" is a tool that helps to organize your day. It simply lists the things that you need to do and allows you to mark them as complete.

• Built with: (HTML5, CSS, JavaScript)

MICROVERSE Remote

Mentor (Volunteer) October, 2022 – Present

Mentored junior web developers, providing technical support through code reviews.

- Proposed improvements to code organization to improve code quality and overall performance.
- Provided advice and tips on how to maintain motivation to maintain longevity in the program.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **MICROVERSE**

August, 2022 - November, 2022

## Remote Full Stack Web Development Program, Full Time

- Spent 1300+ hours mastering algorithms, data structures, and full-stack development while simultaneously developing projects with Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, and Redux.
- Developed skills in remote pair-programming using GitHub, industry-standard gitflow, and daily standups to communicate and collaborate with international remote developers.

Faculte Ibn Zohr

September, 2010 - June, 2013

# Degree, Concentration

- Completed coursework about programming logic and algorithms.
- Completed coursework about PLC programming.